Guide to the Yale University Building Project Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Drawings, 1912-1988; Series II
  - 20:06 Peabody Museum
    - Room 14, 1967 (Box 161)
    - Room 305, 1964-1966 (Box 161)
  - 20:07 Bowers Hall
    - Detail of Cupola, 1931 (Box 162)
    - Roof Truss Tie Rods, 1934 (Box 162)
    - Operating Switches, 1974 (Box 162)
    - Alteration Plans, 1974 (Box 162)
  - 20:09 Yale Computer Center
    - Proposed Alterations: First Floor, 1965 (Box 162)
  - 20:13 Accelerator Laboratory
    - General Construction, 1952 (Box 163)
    - Temperature Controls, 1952 (Box 163)
    - 10 Ton E.T. Crane, 1955 (Box 163)
    - General Construction, 1960 (Box 163)
    - Tandem Accelerator, 1963-1965 (Box 163)
    - Safety Shut-Off, 1966 (Box 163)
    - Fire-Proofing Doors in Generator Room, 1967 (Box 163)
    - Heavy [Ion?] Accelerator: Temperature Control, 1976 (Box 163)
    - Renovations for Room 105, 1979 (Box 163)
    - External Piping for Models, undated (Box 163)
  - 20:14 Gibbs Laboratory
    - West Elevation - Louvers, 1955 (Box 164)
    - Doors and Frames, 1958 (Box 164)
    - Sixth Floor Penthouse, 1958 (Box 164)
    - Cabinets and Tables, 1958 (Box 164)
    - Alterations, 1964 (Box 164)
    - West Elevation - Louvers, 1955 (Box 164)
    - Doors and Frames, 1958 (Box 164)
    - Cabinets and Table, 1958 (Box 164)
    - Sixth Floor Penthouse, 1958 (Box 164)
    - Alterations, 1964 (Box 164)
    - Proposed Sterilizing Facility, Room 424, 1965 (Box 164)
    - Automatic Temperature Control, Air-Conditioning, 1966-1967 (Box 164)
    - Alterations to Particular Rooms, 1966-1967 (Box 164)
    - Doors, Louvers, Chalkboards, Hardware, 1966-1967 (Box 164)
    - Proposed Alterations for Corridor, 1967 (Box 164)
    - Renovations to Sixth Floor, 1979 (Box 164)
    - Sixth Floor, 1981 (Box 164)
    - Sixth Floor Seminar Room, 1982 (Box 164)
    - Alterations to Rooms 322, 323, 324, undated (Box 164)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 164)
  - 20:15 Bingham Oceanographic and Ornithological Laboratory
    - Boring Location Plan, 1956 (Box 165)
    - General Construction, 1957-1958 (Box 165)
    - Proposed Alterations for Lab Rooms, 1966-1967 (Box 165)
    - Elevations and Details, Room 301, 1967 (Box 165)
    - Honeywell Relay Model, 1974 (Box 165)
    - Hot Water Systems, 1982 (Box 165)
  - 20:16 334 Edwards Street
    - Alterations for Computer Installation, 1966 (Box 166)
  - 20:19 Kline Geology Laboratory
    - Standard Wash Chamber for PE-T Cross Draft Book, 1955-1956 (Box 166)
    - Air Distributing Units, 1960 (Box 166)
    - Boring Plans, 1961 (Box 166)
    - Luminous Ceilings, 1962 (Box 166)
    - Fire Alarm, 1962 (Box 166)
    - Darklites and Washlites, 1962 (Box 166)
    - Sedimentation Channel, 1962 (Box 166)
    - Rooms 329, 380, 382, 1962-1963 (Box 166)
    - Electrical Wiring, 1962-1963 (Box 166)
    - Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 166)
    - Plans for Stairs, Entrance, 1963 (Box 166)
    - Elevators, 1963 (Box 166)
    - Switchgear Assembly, 1963 (Box 166)
    - Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 166)
    - Room 16P: Proposed Alterations, 1966 (Box 166)
    - Room 18: Proposed Alterations, 1966 (Box 166)
    - Small Flexible Hoods for Bone Cleaning, 1969 (Box 166)
    - Loading Dock Hoist, 1971 (Box 166)
    - Floor Plans for Basement and Third Floor, 1982 (Box 166)
  - 20:20 Kline Chemistry Laboratory
    - Switchgears, 1963 (Box 167)
    - Darklite, 1963 (Box 167)
    - Proposed Alterations for Nuclear Chemistry Department, 1968 (Box 167)
    - Laboratory and Office Alterations, 1970 (Box 167)
    - Chain Hoist Beam - Room K19, 1971 (Box 167)
    - Hood Exhaust Renovation, 1981 (Box 167)
    - Exhaust Fan, 1982 (Box 167)
  - 20:21 Yale Nuclear Structures Laboratory
    - Control Systems, 1981 (Box 168)
    - Electrical Circuits, 1981 (Box 168)
    - Conversion Yale MP Accelerator: Mechanical, 1985 (Box 168)
  - 20:23 Kline Biology Tower
    - 1 Horizon Tank, 1963 (Box 169)
    - Elevators, 1963 (Box 169)
    - Dumbwaiter, 1964 (Box 169)
    - Underground Additional Proposal, 1964 (Box 169)
    - Perimeter Under-Floor Duct, 1964 (Box 169)
    - Proposed Emergency Generator, 1964 (Box 169)
    - Heating and Ventilation, 1964-1966 (Box 169)
    - Rooms 6436 and 725A: Refrigeration Schematic, 1965 (Box 169)
    - Revolving Doors and Entrances, 1965 (Box 169)
    - Rooms 249, 349, 549: Schematic Diagram, 1965 (Box 169)
    - Electrical: Ninth Floor, 1965-1966 (Box 169)
    - Shop Office: Changes and Additions, 1966 (Box 169)
    - Rooms 643C and 725A: Electrical Schematic, 1966 (Box 169)
    - Sixth Floor: Cargo Caire Unit, 1966 (Box 169)
    - Dr. D. Söll: Proposed Alterations, 1967 (Box 169)
    - Sequenator Installation, 1968 (Box 169)
    - Rooms 700, 702, 704, 702A, 706, 708, 710, 710A, 712, 712A, 754: Proposed Alterations, Elevations, and Details, 1969-1970 (Box 169)
    - Eleventh Floor Renovations, 1978 (Box 169)
    - General Construction, 1980 (Box 169)
    - Replacement of Deionized Water System, 1982 (Box 169)
  - 20:24 354 Edwards
    - Floor Plans - Existing Layout, 1967 (Box 170)
  - 20:25 Pierson-Sage
    - Boiler Plant, 1963 (Box 170)
    - Elevator, 1973 (Box 170)
    - Structural, 1973 (Box 170)
  - 21:06 Yale Divinity School
    - Cabinets, 1932 (Box 171)
    - Kitchen Equipment, 1931-1932 (Box 171)
    - Electrical, 1931-1932 (Box 171)
    - Heating and Ventilation, 1931-1932 (Box 171)
    - Exit Signs, 1931-1932 (Box 171)
    - Toilets, 1931-1932 (Box 171)
    - Gas Meters and Piping, 1932 (Box 171)
    - Plumbing, 1932 (Box 171)
    - Dumbwaiter, 1931 (Box 171)
    - Schedule of Interior Finishes, 1931 (Box 171)
    - Sewer Plan: Power House Section, 1931 (Box 171)
    - General Construction, 1932 (Box 171)
    - Heating and Ventilation, 1956 (Box 171)
    - Plumbing, 1956 (Box 172)
    - Boiler, 1956 (Box 172)
    - Electrical, 1956 (Box 172)
    - Boiler, 1956-1957 (Box 172)
    - Refectory: Proposed Faculty Dining Room, 1962 (Box 172)
    - First Floor: Proposed Snack Bar, 1966 (Box 172)
    - Balcony, 1966 (Box 172)
    - First Floor: Entrance Hall, 1966 (Box 172)
    - Sound Module Plan, 1974 (Box 172)
    - Elevator, 1976 (Box 172)
    - Door, 1981 (Box 172)
  - 21:15 Marsh Botanical Gardens
    - Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 173)
  - 22 Yale Medical School: Trask? Conference Room
    - Air-Conditioning, Electrical, 1963 (Box 174)
  - 22 98 Park St.
    - "As is" Plan and Alterations, 1971 (Box 174)
  - 22:02 Tompkins East
    - Electrical Wiring, 1963 (Box 175)
  - 22:22 Jane Ellen Hope Memorial Building
    - Fire Alarm Systems, 1981 (Box 175)
  - 22:25 Brady Memorial Laboratory
    - Electrical System Renovation, 1964 (Box 176)
    - Ventilation System, 1972-1978 (Box 176)
    - Renovations at Y.P.I. Gym Room, 1976-1977 (Box 176)
  - 22:46 Private Pavilion
    - Electric Cables and Ducts, 1929 (Box 177)
    - Tunnel Under Cedar St., 1929 (Box 177)
  - 22:50 Sterling Hall of Medicine
    - Ventilation, 1927 (Box 178)
    - Library Alterations, 1940 (Box 178)
    - Water Cooling System, 1957-1958 (Box 178)
    - Automatic Temperature Control, 1967 (Box 178)
    - C-Wing Renovation, 1970 (Box 178)
    - Laboratory Alterations, 1970 (Box 178)
    - Laboratory Furniture, 1971 (Box 178)
    - Air-Conditioning, 1972 (Box 179)
    - Environmental Walk-In Rooms, 1972-1973 (Box 179)
    - Fume Hoods Installation, 1973 (Box 179)
    - Library: Heating, Ventilation, Air-Conditioning, undated (Box 179)
  - 22:51 Sterling Power House
    - Chandelier, no date (Box 180)
    - Miscellaneous, 1912-1929 (Box 180)
    - Proposed Force Draft Apparatus, 1917 (Box 180)
    - Power House Courtyard, Alteration to Engine Room, Gate Posts, Metallic Sash for Windows, 1923 (Box 180)
    - Additions, 1929 (Box 180)
    - Engines, 1929 (Box 180)
    - Electrical Connections, 1929 (Box 180)
    - Miscellaneous, 1929 (Box 180)
    - Switchboard, 1930 (Box 180)
    - Side Elevation of Boiler, 1930 (Box 180)
    - Supplement to Turbine Outline, 1931 (Box 180)
    - Pump Foundation, 1931 (Box 180)
    - Piping for Refrigeration System, 1932 (Box 180)
    - Turbine, Gear, and Generating Unit, 1939 (Box 180)
    - Relief Valve, 1940 (Box 180)
    - Support for New Turbine, 1940 (Box 180)
    - Electrical, 1940 (Box 180)
    - Burners, Pump, and Heater Set, 1949 (Box 180)
    - Steam Flow Meters, 1949 (Box 180)
    - Details of Window Box, 1949 (Box 180)
    - Addition, 1957 (Box 180)
    - Economizer Ducts, 1980 (Box 180)
  - 22:71 382 Congress Ave.
    - Air-Conditioning Layout, 1969 (Box 181)
    - Structural Renovations, 1974 (Box 181)
  - 22:75 30 Davenport Ave.
    - Architectural Renovations, undated (Box 181)
  - 22:154 Yale-New Haven Hospital
    - Ventilation, 1974 (Box 182)
  - 22:156 Congress Animal Facility
    - Duct-Work Revisions, 1974 (Box 182)
  - 22:162 Edward S. Harkness Hall
    - Electrical Wiring - Refrigeration, 1954 (Box 182)
    - Piping, 1954 (Box 182)
    - Primary Loop Extensions, 1966 (Box 182)
    - Stairs and Walkway, 1972 (Box 182)
    - Personnel Offices: Renovations, 1976 (Box 182)
  - 22:163 Hunter Laboratory
    - Electrical Schematic Drawings, undated (Box 183)
    - Refrigeration Systems, undated (Box 183)
  - 22:167 Laboratory of Epidemiology and Public Health
    - Ninth Floor Alterations, 1981 (Box 183)
  - 22 School of Medicine
    - Miscellaneous, Unidentified Drawings, 1961-1972 (Box 183)
  - 24:12 Gunther Property (Guilford, CT)
    - Three Sets of Floor Plans, 1969 (Box 184)
    - Biological Field Station, 1970 (Box 184)
  - 25:02 Yale Bowl
    - Proposed New Ticket Buildings, 1974 (Box 184)
  - 25:03 Yale Armory Garage Space
    - Riding Hall, undated (Box 184)
  - 25:04 Yale Golf Course
    - Equipment Storage, 1963 (Box 184)
    - Clubhouse Dining Room Alterations, 1973 (Box 184)
  - 25:05 Lapham Field House: Women's Locker Room Facility
    - Resurfacing Concrete Floor, 1975 (Box 185)
    - Mechanical, 1975 (Box 185)
    - Electrical, 1975 (Box 185)
    - Driveway Drainage, 1978 (Box 185)
  - 25:07 Coxe Cage Renovations
    - Above Grandstand Plan, 1981 (Box 186)
    - Track Timing System Display, 1981 (Box 186)
    - Carpentry, 1981 (Box 186)
    - Electrical, 1981 (Box 186)
    - Metalworking, 1981 (Box 186)
  - 25:08 Athletic Fields
    - Irrigation Plan, 1973-1974 (Box 187)
  - 25:08 Yale Baseball Stadium
    - Special Curtain, 1981 (Box 187)
    - Scoreboard Clock, 1982 (Box 187)
  - 25:10 Cullman Courts
    - Control System, 1972 (Box 187)
  - 26:03 Gale's Ferry Boat House
    - Proposed Alterations: Kitchen, Bathroom, Stairwell, 1975 (Box 188)
  - 26:05 Bob Cook Boat House (Derby, CT)
    - Plumbing Alterations, 1958 (Box 188)
    - Gas Hot Water Heaters Installation, 1958 (Box 188)
    - Renovations: First Floor Doors and Windows, 1970 (Box 188)
    - Proposed First Floor Addition, 1976 (Box 188)
  - 27:05 William Wirt Winchester Hospital
    - Water and Fire Supply System, 1933 (Box 189)
  - 27:11 150 Highland St.
    - Proposed Alterations for Drama Studio, 1966 (Box 189)
  - 27:12 Animal Shelter (Bethany, CT)
    - Aquastat, 1961 (Box 189)
    - Oil Burner, 1961 (Box 189)
    - Dog Bath - Can and Tray Washer, 1961 (Box 189)
  - 27:14 Whitehall Apartments
    - Storm Drainage System, 1967 (Box 190)
    - Trash Enclosures, 1970 (Box 190)
  - 27:17 Sperry Animal Clinic (Bethany, CT)
    - Ventilation, Heating, 1970 (Box 190)
  - 27:18 Haskins Laboratory
    - Sink and Cabinet?, 1969 (Box 190)
    - Duct Layout, 1969 (Box 190)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 191)
- Planning documents for Science Hill projects, Sprague Hall renovations, Sterling Hall of Medicine, and Broadway extension, 2000; Accession 2001-A-033
  Restricted until 1 Jan 2036.
  - Submissions for qualifications for design architects
    - Alexander Gorlin (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Architects and Planners (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Burt Hill Kosar Rittelman Associates (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Butler Rogers Baskett (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Cannon (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Ellerbe Becket (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Flad and Associates (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Fletcher Thompson (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Ford Farewell Mills and Gatsch (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Gwathmey, Siegal and Associates (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - H O and K (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Hardy Holzman Pfeiffer Associates (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Helmuth Obata and Kassabaum (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Hiller (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - HLW International (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Kuwabara Payne McKenna Blumberg (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Mathes Group (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Noyes Vogt (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Payette Associates (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Phillip W. Neuberg (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Porphyrios Associates (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Shepley Bullfinch Richardson and Abbott (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Skidmore Owings and Merrill (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Svigals Associates (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - The Stubbins Associates (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Weiss/Manfredi (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - William Wilson (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Support materials for submissions (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Feasibility study of B-Wing Extension, Sterling Hall of Medicine by Svigals Assoc. (Box 2)
- Project reports, 1994-2003; Accession 2004-A-036
  Restricted until 1 Jan 2039.
  - Memos of meetings (Arts Area) (parts I and II), Undated (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - Report on Jewish Community Center (Arts Area), Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Charge to committee by provost; miscellaneous names and addresses, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Assignment plans, space inventory (Arts Area), Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Yale School of Drama spacial analysis, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Planning Study (Draft Bibliography Arts Area), 94101801, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 94101801, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 94101801, Planning Study (Yale Arts Area), 1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 94101801, Costs (Arts Area), 1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 94101801, Art Gallery Information, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 94101801, Polshek and Partners (Arts Area), 1996 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 94101801, Polshek and Partners Qualifications, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 94101801, Renovations (Arts Area) (parts I and II), 1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 94101801, Polshek Meetings (Arts Area), Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 94101801, Paul Rudolph Drawings (Arts Area), 1995 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 94101801, YUAG Vogel to Polshek, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 94101801, Space Inventory System (Arts Area), 1996 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 94101801, School of Art, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 94101801, Physical Plant Zone (Arts Area), 1994 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 94101801, Maintenance Cost (Arts Area), 1990-1995 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 94101801, Facility Spending (Arts Area), 1989-1994 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 94101801, Financial Reports (Arts Area), 1995 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - 94101801, WES Files Plan Room (Arts Area), 1994 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 94101801, Space Summary (Arts Area), 1995 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - 94101801, York Chapel Planning Study (Arts Area) (parts I, II, and III), 1990 (Box 1, Folder 26-28)
  - 94101801, Goals for Arts Area, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - 94101801, Preliminary Planning Report (Arts Area), 1991 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - 94101801, McKinnell Report (Arts Area), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 94101801, Study Background (Arts Area), 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 2-3)
  - 94101801, Study Report (Arts Area), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 94101801, Jackson, Bohlin Architecture Catalog, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 94101801, Atkin, Olshin, Lawson-Bell and Associates Architects Catalog, Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 94101801, Finegold Alexander and Associates Inc. Catalog, Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 94101801, Smith Edwards Architects Catalog, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 94101801, Timothy Dwight College Renovation, Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 94101801, Vitetta Group Architecture Catalog (parts I and II), Undated (Box 2, Folder 10-11)
  - 94101801, McClier Architecture Catalog, Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 94101801, McClier Firm Proposal for Services Timothy Dwight College Renovations, Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 94101801, Allean Greenberg Architect Proposal for TD Renovations (parts I, II, and III), Undated (Box 2, Folder 14-16)
  - 94101801, Goody, Clancy and Associates Proposal for TD Renovations, Undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - 94101801, Goody, Clancy and Associates Catalog, Undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - 94101801, Peter Gosolfi Associates Proposal for TD Renovations, Undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 94101801, Comprehensive Renovation Request for Proposal TD College, Yale (parts I and II), Undated (Box 2, Folder 20-21)
  - 94101801, Fee Proposal for Timothy Dwight College, Undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - 94101801, Selection Letters for Timothy Dwight College Architect, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 94101801, Architect Tour Schedule for Timothy Dwight College, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 94101801, Timothy Dwight Architect Acceptance and Rejection Letters, Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 94101801, Facility Identification Forms, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 94101801, Timothy Dwight College Consultants to be Considered, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 94101801, Architect Apllications for Timothy Dwight College, Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 94101801, History of Timothy Dwight, Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 94101801, Conctacts for Timothy Dwight, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Yale University "Campus Plan", Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Capital Project Manual, Undated (Box 3, Folder 10-11)
  - Yale standard specifications, Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Yale University Guidebook for New Buildings, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Capital Plan (Rebuilding Yale), 1988 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Agreement between Coughlin, Mr. and Mrs. John E., 1951 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Agreement between design and construction of barn at Smith-Harris, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Agreement between First Ammendment to supply gas, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Agreement between New Vault Drama school, Vault in front of Art Gallery, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Agreement between Use of gas for children's hospital, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Agreement between Yale and Mitchell/Giurgola Associates on Undergraduate Residential Housing Project, Undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Agreement between Yale and Portable Parking Structures of New England, Inc. on design and consulting contract, Undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Agreement between Anthony Trust Association and Yale, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Agreement between Cesar Pelli and Associates and Yale, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Agreement between Covington Trust Association and Yale, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Agreement between Douglas Orr and Yale, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Agreement between Eta Chapter of Zeta Psi Association and Yale, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Agreement between George B.H. Macomber and Power Strut, Incorporated, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Agreement between Kingsley Trust and Yale, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Agreement between Mory's and Assn. and Yale, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Agreement between N.W. Ayer and Son, Inc. and Yale, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Agreement between Paul Rudolph and Yale for the School of Forestry, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Agreement between Stone Trust Corporation and Yale, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Agreement between the Elizabethan Club and Yale, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Agreement between the Phelps Association and Yale, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Agreemeent between the Winthrop Trust Association and Yale, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Agreement between Trumbull Trust Assn. and Yale, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Agreement between Yale and J.H. Hogan Inc. for renovations to 77 Prospect Street, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Agreement between Yale and H.E. Murdock and Sons, for renovation on Yale Repertory Theater, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Agreement between Yale and J.H. Hogan on golf cart storage facility, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Agreement between Yale and Lydia Straus-Edwards, AIA-Central Area telephone ducts, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Agreement between Yale and Russel Trust association regarding furnishing of steam, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Agreement between Yale and Tomlinson, Hawley and Patterson Renovation of W.L. Harkness Hall, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Agreement between Yale Daily News and Yale, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Agreement for alterations for Concilium between Yale and Total Building and Design Company, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Agreement for Building to be built for library, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Agreement for Nursing Building on 38 South Street, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Agreement for the construction of the new Music Center Building-Gruen Associates, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Agreement for the interruptable gas service, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Agreement for the manufacture and installation of bookstacks for the Seeley G. Mudd Library, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Agreement of lease for suites 1B, 1P and 1Q at Crown Court, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Agreement on 86 Wall St-Naples Pizza, between Yale and William Greenhouse, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Agreement on architectural services to the existing Gallery of Fine Arts to the Garvan Collection, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Agreement on Greeley Memorial Laboratory between Yale and Tor, Shapiro Associates, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Agreement on the installation of chilled water service to the Memorial Unit, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Agreement on Yale University Theatre fire protection and Yale Cabaret fire protection, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Agreement to construct an equipment base station and antenna structure, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Agreement: Alleyway between Church and Mason Laboratory, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Agreement on alterations to existing building at 266-268 York St. (Architect-Lydia Straus-Edwards), 19845 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Agreement on construction of Brady-Boardman Connector (Office of Douglas Orr, Winder and Associates), 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Agreement between Yale and Davis Cochran Miller Baerman Noyes for office building at 33 Whitney, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Contract: air conditioning, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Contract: Amendments-consulting contract covering the Sterling Boiler Plant, Yale University, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Certificates of insurance, locations-Yale, 50 Ashmun St. 44 Ashmun, 335 Prospect, 104 Prospect, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Central power plant chilled water installation to new Engineering and Applied Science Building, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Agreement: Clean air device service agreement, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - University Health Center construction of a Health Center/Hillhouse Avenue, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Consultant services for physical planning and development, Yale University, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Consulting engineer agreement between Yale University and Mr. John C. Martin, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Contract - alterations to Yale Computer Center/Tomlinson and Hawley, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Contract - Douglas Orr and Yale for the construction of the addition to the building, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Contract - master plan for architectural service (Yale and Yale-New Haven Hospital), 1967 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Contract between Yale and Grabe Contract Designs, Inc. for exhibit and display work at Garvan Galleries, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Contract between Yale and Kallamann and Mckinnell for Grove Whitney Garage, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Contract between Yale University and Dwight Building Company, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Contract between Yale University, Employment and Training Association of New Haven, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Contract between Yale University and George B. H. Macombre Company, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Contract between Yale University and Pellecchia and Meyers Architects, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 18)